Yeah, we'll take the "A-M"
from Amy and, uh,
the "Y" from Emily.
(Raj:)That's just Amy.
(Sheldon:)Exactly.
See how well we work together?
(Penny:)And in double-blind
studies,
(Penny:)Placinex proved extremely
effective in treating
(Penny:)all kinds of anxiety.
(Penny:)Actually, funny story...
the boys in the lab
(Penny:)were worried about getting
FDA approval for Placinex;
(Penny:)they started taking it,
stopped worrying.
(Sheldon:)Got it.
(Penny:)Uh, do you have any questions?
(Dr Gallo:)Just one.
Mm-hmm?
(Dr Gallo:)When you made your husband
pretend to be a patient
(Dr Gallo:)so you could get access to me,
what were you thinking there?
(Penny:)I just... meant a question
about the drug.
(Dr Gallo:)Yeah, I know what you meant.
(Dr Gallo:)Let's put that aside
for a minute
(Dr Gallo:)and talk about
why you married Leonard.
(whispers):
I don't wanna.
(Dr Gallo:)Here is a man
raised by an overbearing woman
(Dr Gallo:)who completely dominated every
aspect of his formative years.